

# CONTACT

kevinjones.engineer
github.com/joneskj55
linkedin.com/in/joneskj55
joneskj55@gmail.com

# **ABOUT ME**

I am a veteran, technologist, lifelong learner & open source enthusiast. My focus is on taking my software development skills to the next level. I am a chronic open-source contributor and have a lot of experience with distributed collaboration. I am a team player and clear communicator who focuses on team success. Currently, I am working on mastering the MEAN stack.

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### **NEWTON**

MOBILE APPLICATION DEVELOPER

Develops, maintains, and deploys decentralized applications to meet the needs of decentralized finance customers and crypto users. Tech: React Native, Node.js, CSS, Git, JavaScript, TypeScript, XCode, VSCode, Android Studio. Jun 2022 - Present

#### **JAMBB**

WEB DEVELOPER

Architects, maintains, and deploys smart contracts and decentralized applications to meet the needs of hundreds of thousands of fans. Tech: Docker, Node.js, Cadence, Solidity, Hardhat, IPFS, Nuxt, Vue, Tailwind, Git, TypeScript. Jan 2022 - Jun 2022

#### FARM BUREAU BANK

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Responsible for the development and maintenance of internal and external web applications and tools. Writes, tests, develops and implements custom programs to streamline financial institution workflows. Tech: jQuery, HTML, CSS, MySQL. May 2019 - Jan 2022

### **CNF TECHNOLOGIES**

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER (CONTRACT)

Responsible for developing and maintaining the full stack of a website utilized by the U.S. Air Force to maintain and track data on cryptographic products.

Tech: ASP.NET, jQuery, HTML, CSS, MySQL DataTables, Bootbox, Font Awesome & Bootstrap. Mar - Dec 2018

## **EDUCATION**

# **SKILLS**

BELLEVUE UNIVERSITY

2020 - 2022 | BS Web Development

CODEUP

2016 - 2017 | Full-Stack Web Development Certificate JavaScript Git
TypeScript CSS
Node.js HTML
Vue.js Express
React MongoDB
Angular Tailwind